# KAREL VERSCHRAEGEN

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 



# **PROFILE**

I have spent the last 4+ years focused on all aspects of software development, ranging from creating applications in React and Vue to building backends in NestJS and PHP.

I have proven success in rapid prototyping, product development, leadership, technical problem-solving, coordination and communication.

- karelverschraegen.com
- github.com/KarelVerschraegen/
- karelverschraegenbiz@gmail.com
- Q Ghent, Belgium

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER - AIKIDO**

February 2023 - May 2023

- Help discover product-market-fit with newly built features by rapidly prototyping and iterating based on collected feedback
- Improve onboarding experience, open-source license scanning...

### **TECH LEAD - CHEQROOM**

July 2022 - February 2023

- Manage and host scrum meetings (stand-ups, sprint reviews...)
- Communicate and coordinate feature releases and bug fixes
- Unblock team members, provide feedback and technical insights
- Tackle technical debt, large refactors and general maintenance

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER - CHEQROOM**

July 2019 - July 2022

- Set up a communication layer between Knockout and React
- Build out design system and accompanying component library
- · Set up and deploy GraphQL microservices on AWS
- Automate the deployment process via GitHub Actions

## **INTERN - RIALTO**

February 2019 - May 2019

- · Learn React, Redux and TypeScript
- Build a floorplan drawing tool based on SVG's

# **SKILLS**

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication and coordination
- Leadership
- Problem solver
- Independent
- Curious

#### HARD SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React, Vue
- NestJS, NodeJS
- PHP
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL

# **EDUCATION**

## APPLIED COMPUTER SCIENCE

Hogeschool Gent (2016 - 2019)